ILR School Administrative Assistant Files /4009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Administrative Assistant Files
1951-1956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4009
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists mainly of correspondence. Also includes files on the Extention Offices, and Foreign Programs.
3082789
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3082789
- Inst. Of Int'l. Indus. And Labor Relations Progress Report 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NYSSILR Extension Booklet (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Advisory Council Report - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- SU-2 State Univ. General Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- F-8 NYSS of ILR Statements, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- EQ-2 IBM Installation, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Inst. Of Int'l Indus. And Labor Rel. Progress Report 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Report on Faculty 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dean Report to President 1950-51, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ILR Report to President Committee on Long Range Planning - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILR Report to President's Committee on Long Range Planning - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ILR Report to 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual Report to State University 1950-51, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Misc., 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Financial Statement 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Dorothy Fennell - NYSSILR (Box 1, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 Applicants -- A-B, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- C-G, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 L, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- L-N, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 Mac, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- G-1-2 Mc, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- G-1-2 N, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- O-S, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- G-1-2 P, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- T-Z, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 T, 1944-1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- G-1-2 R, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- G-1-2 U, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- G-1-2 V, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- G-1-2 W, 1948-1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- S - cont), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 Y, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- G-1-2 Applicants (American Ideals), 1952 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- E-6 Contact Forms, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- B-3-3 Elmira Office, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- E-1-1 Office Space Assignment, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- B-3-1 Albany Office, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- B-3-2 Buffalo Office, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- A-4 Organization Chart of ILR School (Box 3, Folder 6)
- B-3-5 Rented Campus Space, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- B-3-6 Olean, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- B-1-2 Class Room Scheduling, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- B-1 Sage Green, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- B-3-4 New York Metropolitan Office, 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- G-2 General Outside Correspondence A-Z, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Con-1 Correspondence w. Conference Sec'y, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- G-1 Inter-Office Memos (All Staff, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- G-1-2 Memos to Non-Professional Staff, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- G-1-1 Memos to Faculty, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- J- Inst. Of Internat. ILR, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- P-6-1 Notes on Office Hours and Vacations, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- G-1-2 Stenciled Memos to Staff + Faculty 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Memo's to Staff 1948 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Comm. - 7 IRRA - Local Chapter, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Com-5 Graduate Student Council, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Com-4 ILR Student Council, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Com-3 Fire Prevention Committee, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Com-2 Graduate Committee, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Com-1 ILR Staff Organization, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Business Office - 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Applicants - Professional, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- P-I Administration and Faculty, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- P-4-2 Graduate Assistantship Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- P-4-1 Grad. Assistantship Policy and Procedure, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- O-1-1 Machines--Repair and Maintenance, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- O-1-3 Requests for Equipment, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- C-8 Building and Grounds, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- C-2-2-a Supply Room--Quarterly Report, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Advisory Council 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Faculty Meetings 1954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Materials Laboratory - 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Materials Laboratory - 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Extension Office-Ithaca-1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Extension Office - Albany 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Extension Office - Buffalo 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Extension Office, N.Y.C. 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Extension Office - Ithaca - General 1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Student Personnel - General Corresp. '49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Extension Office - Ithaca - General 1954 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- L-2 Library General, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- L-1 Library Budget, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- RI-1 Resident Instruction General Corresp., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- R1-2 Accessory Instruction, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- R1-3 Course Schedules, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- R1-4 Lab Fee Charges, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- E-2 Extension Office -- Albany, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- M-2 Materials Lab -- Monthly Reports, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- R-1 Research General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- R-2 Research Projects (Non-Fiscal), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- E-3 Extension Office -- Buffalo, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- E-5 Extension Office -- NY Metropolitan, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- PR Public Relations, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- E-4 Extension Office -- Central District, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Navy Gunners Research Project #7032, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Misc., 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- F-10 Buffalo Manpower Study, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- ECA Turkish Program, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Turkish E.C.A. - TA -77-49 Memorandum, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Turkish ECA Correspondence Project TA-77-49, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Turkish Program, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- R. Corvini Expense Account 9/10-20, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Reimbursement Requested by Turks + Mades to Them, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Requests for Checks, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- TA-77-49 Vouchers + Bills, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Norwegian Team Project TA-48-67 Correspondence, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Norwegian Team Project TA-48-67 Programs, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Norwegian Project Team TA-48-67 General Information and Press Releases, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Norwegian Team Project TA-48-67 Accounts (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Ann Douglas The Mediation Process 7006, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- German E.C.A., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- State Dept. German Trainees 1951-52, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- German Mar. 30, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- German(Faded Text), 1952 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- French Team Project TA-38-87 Programs, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- French Team Project General Information + Press Releases TA-38-87, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- French-Team Project TA-38-87 Correspondence, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 8)